(Amy:)You slept with him?
(Penny:)I didn't know what else to do.
He had those big, sad eyes.
(Bernadette:)Oh, sure, you had no choice.
(Penny:)He looked at me like this.
(Amy:)If that's all it takes,
it's a good thing you don't have a dog.
(Bernadette:)Don't worry, you'll have plenty
of chances to break up with him.
(Bernadette:)Your wedding day, your honeymoon,
your 50th anniversary.
(Penny:)Look, it's fine,
we're not getting married, okay?
(Penny:)We're keeping things, you know,
homeostasis.
(Amy:)It's so cute when she tries.
(Penny(phone text tone):)It's from Leonard.
"Last night was amazing.
You're amazing.
I'm so lucky to have you in my life."
(Penny(phone text tone):)Okay, stop it.
(Howard:)Hey, Bernie, guess what? I stood up
to the other astronauts like you said.
And I gotta tell you last night
was the first time in a week...
(Howard:)...I got a good night's sleep.
(Bernadette:)Oh, Howie.
(Howard:)What's wrong? You look upset.
(Sheldon(measures):)Nope.
(Bernadette:)This is my proud face.